

Yang Li

Professional Summary

Veteran Computer Repair Technician offering 3 months of experience delivering on-site and remote repair services. Expert at replacing and upgrading assets ranging from desktop components to printers and user interface peripherals. Dedicated to maintaining consistent data privacy policies. Known for providing quick, efficient repair services under strict time constraints.

Work History

Dalhousie University - AI Robot

Halifax, NS

03/2017 - Current

- Built, configured or tested robots or robotic applications.
- Outlined and programmed routines and parameters for different robotic systems.
- Evaluated proposed and existing robotics systems to check quality and safety controls.
- Created applications to meet diverse needs and design requirements.
- Increase robot's task completion speed by 10%

Online - Computer Repair Technician

Halifax, NS

06/2018 - Current

- Researched and identified problems with computers and advised staff and clients on plans of action.
- Disassembled computers to perform diagnostics and check for repair needs.
- Assessed system hardware and software and suggested modifications to reduce lag time and improve overall speed.
- Responded to support requests from end users and patiently walked individuals through basic troubleshooting tasks.
- Wrote reports on computer statuses and maintenance jobs.
- Managed over 50 customer calls per day

Junior High School - Model airplane

Zhengzhou, Henan

03/2012 - Current

★ tendernesscurtain@gmail.com

902 410 4586

Toronto, ON M1H3J7

Skills

- Computer troubleshooting
- Computer assistance
- Computer skills
- Computer networks
- Computer programming
- Computer knowledge
- Computer science
- Security issues troubleshooting
- Software Installation
- Repair

Education

09/2020

Dalhousie University

Halifax, NS

Associate of Science: Computer Science

- Member of [Chinese Students' Federation]
- Completed professional development in [UI Setting]
- Member of [Film club]

- Quickly learned new skills and applied them to daily tasks, improving efficiency and productivity.
- Maintained energy and enthusiasm in fast-paced environment.
- Worked to maintain outstanding attendance record, consistently arriving to work ready to start immediately.
- Study 20 days can make good model

Hobbies

For computer-related knowledge, and have considerable hands-on skills and experience in learning artificial intelligence and robots, have a strong curiosity for high-tech products or technologies.